<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>archive on I&#39;m A Super .com</title>
    
    
    
    <link>http://www.imasuper.com/tags/archive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in archive on I&#39;m A Super .com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>I&#39;m A Super .com</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.imasuper.com/tags/archive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 Presidential Debates - What you don&#39;t know</title>
      <link>http://www.imasuper.com/2016/10/10/2016-presidential-debates-what-you-dont-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.imasuper.com/2016/10/10/2016-presidential-debates-what-you-dont-know/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Until 1988, the League of Women Voters had organized and moderated the Presidential Debates as an independent 3rd party.
They were responsible for moderation, selection of questions, location, and other details related to the debates. The only thing the candidates had to do, was show up.
In 1987, the Democratic and Republican Party then jointly created a non-profit organization called the Commission on Presidential Debates. This commission secretly created a contract called a memorandum of understanding that decided which candidates would participate in the debates, which individuals would be panelists capable of asking questions, who could be in the audience… even the height of the podiums!
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fried Green Tomatoes – The movie’s horribly nasty secret</title>
      <link>http://www.imasuper.com/2008/12/29/fried-green-tomatoes-the-movies-horribly-nasty-secret/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.imasuper.com/2008/12/29/fried-green-tomatoes-the-movies-horribly-nasty-secret/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Warning: This article is really only relevant to you if you’ve seen the movie Fried Green Tomatoes (1991) and have a reasonable memory of it.
Ever since I saw Fried Green Tomatoes many moons ago, I considered it one of my semi-favorite movies. Probably not in my top 10, but definitely in my top 20. However, something has always bothered me about it.
The primary character of Fried Green Tomatoes is Idgie Threadgoode.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>